What the heck are you doing here?
Nothing at all.
If it's nothing, you wouldn't be sitting
here looking like you lost your way.
Did something happen?
Not really.
There's hair all over your uniform.
Were you playing with a
dog or cat or something?
I wasn't playing! I just...
I wanted to rescue a cat
that was stuck in this tree.
Oh, so that's what happened.
Stay right there. Don't you dare move.
Crus—
Easy to tear by hand
Surgical Tape
...for cuts and scratches...
World-Famous...
Shiina. Take off your tights.
Huh?
Come on, don't look at me like that.
Here. You can use my jacket and I'll
turn around, so take off your tights.
After we ice your injury,
I'll put a compress on it.
How could you tell?
Because you have one shoe half off
and you haven't tried to stand up.
Spraining your foot while saving a cat.
What a cliché story.
Oh, you be quiet!
Fine, fine.
Go on. Take off your tights
and let me see your foot.
Surgical
...with World-Famous Water
Crushed
Does it feel any better?
Well, a little bit.
Okay, I'll put the compress on.
Don't get mad and call me
a pervert or anything.
I would never say something
that rude to my rescuer!
That's a relief.
You're surprisingly good at that.
Yeah, I can treat minor injuries.
Can't cook, though.
That should be good.
Math
Yes?
Look at your foot.
I don't think you can wear tights
on top of a compress.
Don't worry, they're clean.
Here, this too.
Huh?
You want people to see you
getting carried around?
Excuse me?
Sorry about this.
It's no trouble.
Even I'm enough of a gentleman
that I wouldn't abandon an
injured person or make them walk.
Thank you very much for today.
You really saved me.
No problem.
Okay, take care.
Fujimiya
Oh...
Hey, Amane...
Were you always so hot-blooded
that you wore shorts all year?
Oh, come on. I forgot my sweats.
What a derp!
Shove it.
Next!
Kadowaki-kun, go for it!
Our prince!
The prince is as popular as always.
He just waved at me!
Yeah, I guess.
You don't seem to care much.
No. For classmates, we've barely even talked.
Damn it.
That jerk.
But "prince" and "angel" and all that...
Our school sure has some
embarrassing nickn—
See that? The angel just smiled at me!
No, at me!
Yes! I'll show Shiina-san what I'm made of!
Thank you for your help yesterday.
Here's your meal and the clothes you lent me.
How are you feeling?
The pain is already mostly gone.
But I'm avoiding exercise
until I recover fully.
You're still a super popular angel, though.
Huh?
That one little smile
lit a fire under those guys.
I asked you to please stop calling me that!
But that was bewildering to me, too.
Does it really make them that happy?
Yeah, most guys would freak out
if a beautiful girl smiled at them.
Girls, too, right? They were squealing
after Kadowaki waved at them.
Kadowaki?
Oh, that very popular person?
You're not at all interested in him?
Not really.
Different class and all that.
Huh. Is that how it works?
If looking good is all it takes
for other people to develop feelings,
then shouldn't you
develop feelings for me, too?
So you're aware of how cute you are.
It'd be impossible to ignore
the way everyone fawns over me.
Also, objectively speaking,
I know I have good features,
and I've never neglected my appearance.
Quite so.
Today's looks special!
That's for helping me out.
You really didn't have to...
There's korokke?! Did you make it?
I did.
Please reheat it in the
microwave before you eat.
Thank you!
But, you know... I'd love to eat it
freshly made sometime.
Are you trying to come over?
Huh?
Ah, that's not what I meant!
I wouldn't be that pushy when you've
been kind enough to share with me.
Let's split it.
If we split the cost, and I can cook
at your place, I'll consider it.
Huh?
Oh...
Splitting the cost would
actually be ideal for me, too,
especially since I've been
mooching off of you all this time.
But aren't you afraid for your safety?
If you dare make a move,
I'll crush them. Literally.
They'll never work again.
Oh, god! You terrified them into hiding!
You understand the risk now,
so I doubt you'll try anything.
And I believe you understand
the position I hold at school, too.
If I tried anything, I'd get pulverized.
Another thing...
What is it?
I don't think I'm your type anyway.
What if you had been my type?
Then you'd probably be
pestering me all the time.
And then I would have
stayed far away from you.
So I guess I made the grade.
Well, I can at least acknowledge
that you're not a threat.
That's good to know.
In order for Shiina to cook at my place,
we decided on a few conditions.
In addition to paying
half the cost of the ingredients,
I pay her a little extra for the labor.
Fujimiya
If we have other plans
and can't eat together,
we let each other know one day ahead.
And we share the work
of shopping and cleaning up.
They look brand new,
like they've never been used before.
Shut up.
I took the liberty of selecting the menu
myself today. Is that all right?
As long as it's edible,
I'm good with anything.
I'm going to start cooking now,
so please go wait in the living room.
Will do.
I know there's nothing I can help with.
You're certainly taking this gracefully.
Since you can't cook, I wouldn't want
you hovering over me anyway.
You sure don't mince words.
Because it's the truth.
There's no reason to pretend otherwise.
Why do I feel like I've found my wife?
You aren't thinking something gross, are you?
Q-Quit imagining weird stuff!
Thank you for waiting.
Please help yourself.
Wow, it looks delicious!
Thank you for saying that.
Please begin, before it gets cold.
Thank you for the food.
It's great!
Thank you very much.
You certainly seem to be enjoying it.
Because it's honestly delicious.
It's good to show
appreciation for delicious food.
Yes, I guess so...
Also, instead of eating in silence,
wouldn't we both feel better
if I'm up front about how good it is?
I think you're right.
Fujimiya-san?
Ahh! No, it's nothing.
Thank you very much.
You are very welcome.
It was delicious.
I could tell by looking at you.
But it almost feels too good to be true.
Is it really okay for me to dine
with you like this every day?
If it wasn't, I wouldn't have suggested it.
Even so, is it normal to cook
for a guy you don't even like?
I do it because you have
such an unhealthy lifestyle!
Also, I just really like cooking,
and I don't mind watching you eat
since you seem to enjoy it so much.
Yeah, but still...
If it bothers you that much,
I don't need to cook.
No! Please keep cooking!
Then please accept it openly.
Sure.
The Angel Next Door
Spoils Me Rotten
All right, time's up.
Pass your tests up from the back.
It's over, it's over!
Oh, man...
That was too hard!
Amane! How'd you do?
Normal.
Not great, not horrible.
But you still managed to squeeze into
the top 30 scores. You intellectual, you.
That's because I'm not always
so busy flirting that I forget to study.
Having a girlfriend is great, though!
Yeah, sure.
You're such a bland guy.
I bet you'd change
if you met a girl you like.
Ikkun!
Oh, Chi!
Let's go home!
You're really shameless with the PDA.
Patting your cute girlfriend's
head is totally normal.
That's beyond comprehension.
Nah, nah. You're the type of guy who
would totally dote on his girlfriend.
Huh? What?!
Amane has a girlfriend?!
No way.
Aww, why not?
If you did, I'd wanna be close friends.
Your friendship gets a little too close.
I'd feel bad for my imaginary girlfriend.
What?! You have an imaginary girlfriend?!
We were talking about if I got one...
Thank you for washing the dishes.
Sure.
What are you doing there?
I'm grading.
Well, I can see that.
So what's your score?
As long as my essay is right,
it should be perfect.
Why am I not surprised?
I like studying well enough.
And I've studied ahead and already
covered next year's curriculum.
Yikes! That's crazy.
Nice work.
But you do a decent amount of
studying, too, don't you, Fujimiya-san?
Did you see my scores?
I can more or less remember the people who
rank high enough to have their names posted.
Well, that's one condition for me
living alone. Maintaining my grades.
I study enough to stay out of trouble,
but not as much as you.
You sure work hard.
I work hard because I have to.
It's about time for me to be on my way.
Yeah.
Hey!
Full Name
Date of Birth
December 6
Here. You dropped it.
Student ID
Oh, sorry for the trouble.
Well then, have a good night.
Good night.
Her birthday is in four days.
Huh?
I just mean, is there anything you want?
Why ask all of a sudden?
Well, you don't seem to need
a lot of things. I was just curious.
So blunt again...
Hmm. Let me think.
What do I need...
What I want is...
Oh!
Sharpening Stone
A sharpening stone.
Sharpening stone?!
I already have several, but I want
one with a finer grit, you know?
Are you really a high school girl?!
Please don't expect me to behave
like a typical high school girl.
A high school girl who sharpens knives?
How could this be?
I guess I'm a rare find. Lucky for you.
Good morning.
Yeah, good morning.
Hmm. A birthday present?
You know, it's important to do
research into that sort of thing.
It's the key to a good
relationship. Really is.
I told you, she isn't my girlfriend.
Well, it depends on how close you are,
but trinkets and consumables
are usually safe.
That makes sense.
Also, hand cream never fails to please.
It's pretty useful at any age
and it doesn't go bad quickly.
Hand cream, huh?
What's that, what's that?
A birthday present?
You're giving it to a girl, right?
Tell me all about her!
She's a female acquaintance
of mine who's relatively young.
Beyond that, I exercise
my right to remain silent.
But you know, if I have no clue
about her style or personality,
I can't give you helpful advice.
Just go with your instincts.
What gift do you think
would make a girl happy?
Fine, I can see you don't want to tell.
Hmm. What would be good?
I don't know what kind of
relationship you have,
but for an acquaintance
you're fine talking to...
If you want something casual,
you could try candy or a handkerchief
or a bag or something small.
If you gave me some kind of fancy accessory,
I'd think, "What is this? A bribe?" Probably.
What would I ever bribe you for?
So, small trinkets and
things are probably safe.
Also, cute stuff, you know?
Like stuffed animals.
Stuffed animals?
Oh? You like that one?
But a guy my age carrying
a stuffed animal to the counter...
Don't be a coward!
Chitose.
Would you...
Would I?
Please come shopping with me?!
Well, I don't know...
Please. I'm begging you!
Hmm... I guess I could go along with you.
By the way, Amane-kun, I'm kinda
in the mood for something sweet.
Crêpes?
Please allow me to treat you!
Yeah, sure! I'll order the deluxe one!
For you.
What's all this about?
It's your birthday, isn't it?
It is, but...
Would you mind explaining how you knew?
I don't believe I've told anybody at all.
Your school ID.
Remember how you dropped it the other day?
Oh.
You should have just ignored it.
I never celebrate my birthday anyway.
Fine, then.
Then take it as a token of gratitude.
Let's just say I thought
that I owed you something.
Is it all right if I open it?
I'm sorry it isn't anything special,
but you do all that housework for me,
and this looks like it's
really good for the hands.
That's very practical.
I think it's safe to say you usually
lean toward practical things.
I think you're right. Thank you very much.
But there's something else in the bag.
That's just, you know,
a bonus item I picked out on a whim.
A bear?
So, if you don't like it,
you can get rid of it.
I would never do that!
O-Oh.
Yeah, that doesn't sound
like something you'd do.
I would never do something so cruel.
I'll cherish it.
I shouldn't have looked!
Damn it.
I've never received something
like this before.
Huh?
But girls as popular as you
usually get buried in gifts.
Do you really think of me like...
I've never told anyone my birthday.
Because I hate birthdays.
Normally, I get nervous about receiving
presents and things from strangers
and people I don't know well,
so I don't accept them.
But you're accepting this.
Because, Fujimiya-san, you're not a stranger.
Patting your cute girlfriend's
head is totally normal.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
That was close!
Thank you very much, Fujimiya-san.
Dinner with the Angel
Next Time