What are you doing out here?
Fujimiya-san.
Can I help you with something?
That was the first time.
That was the first time
I talked to Mahiru Shiina.
Meet the Angel
No, I don't need anything.
It's just, if you sit out here in the rain
like this, people are gonna worry.
Is that right?
Well, I appreciate your concern,
but I'm here by choice,
so please don't trouble yourself over me.
You'll catch a cold. Go home with this.
I don't need it back.
Thank you. Very... much.
Seijo High School
Amane, keep it down.
Weren't you fine yesterday, man?
I got caught in the rain.
That's not so bad.
But wait, didn't you have an umbrella?
I gave it to someone.
You lent your umbrella
to someone when it was pouring?
When did you become such a softie?
Who'd you lend it to?
A lost girl I passed on the way.
Well, aren't you nice.
That's right.
She looked like she was lost.
Good morning, Shiina-san!
Good morning.
Hey, hey, Shiina-san, listen to this.
Sure. What is it?
The angel. She's super angelic today.
Yeah.
An angel.
That's what everyone at school
calls Mahiru Shiina.
She's attractive and graceful,
gets excellent grades,
First                Year
Combined 12-subject test scores for first term finals
1. Mahiru Shiina 1181 pts.
2. Rika Aizawa 1142 pts.
3. Masahiro Kitazawa 1113 pts.
4. Akane Nishikawa 1090 pts.
5. Hiroki Yusa 1025 pts.
6. Kanako Hasegawa 1005 pts.
7. Mikiya Suzuki 984 pts.
8. Satoshi Ichijo 900 pts.
9. Ryoichi Hara 871 pts.
and her test scores are top of the class.
And she's even good at sports.
But she's still humble and modest.
She's that kind of angel,
so of course she's popular.
I'm sure most of the guys
in class want to date her.
But that's a world I'm not part of.
Don't you wish you had
a girlfriend to take care of you?
Shut up.
Chitose Shirakawa
Wanna come over tonight?
Quit bragging about having one.
This isn't good at all.
You didn't need to bring it back.
Of course I'm going to
return what I borrowed.
Um, you look like you have a fever.
That's none of your business.
But you lent me your umbrella...
You didn't ask me to. It doesn't matter.
Yes, it does!
You caught a cold
because I was sitting there.
Forget about it already.
You don't need to worry about me.
Fujimiya
B-But I...
Just drop it. See yo—
I can't leave you alone like this.
I'm going to repay the favor.
I'm coming in.
I hope you'll excuse me,
but there's no other way.
I can't bear to look at this.
I'm going to step out for a moment,
so why don't you get changed before I return.
Will you do that?
You're seriously coming back?
If I leave you alone to doze off like this,
you won't sleep well.
Shiina
I'd rather bite off my tongue
than tell anyone at school this,
but I started living alone in high school,
and in the same apartment complex,
Shiina
literally next door, lives the angel herself.
What time is it?
It's 7 p.m.
You slept for about two hours.
I brought it from home.
Thanks for that.
It's okay.
Do you have an appetite?
Hmm...
Yeah, a little bit.
You do?
I've made some rice porridge,
so you should have some.
Huh? Your home cooking, Shiina?
If you don't want it, I'll eat it myself.
Uh, no, I mean, I'll eat it! Please let me!
I'll bring it over,
so please take your temperature.
Would you please at least wait
until I leave the room?!
Yeah.
I never knew why the other guys
kept saying she's so cute,
but I think I'm starting to get it.
What was your temperature?
38.3 degrees.
I'll be fine with medicine and some sleep.
Over-the-counter medicine
only treats the symptoms.
You need to get some proper rest
and let your immune system do its job, okay?
Here you go. It shouldn't be too hot.
Thank you.
What is it now?
Do you expect me to feed you?
Huh?
I regret to inform you
that is not a service I provide.
Nobody even asked for that.
But...
I'm just impressed that you can cook.
I live alone, so of course I can.
But for you, Fujimiya-san,
before learning to cook,
you really should try cleaning your room.
You are quite right.
It's good!
Well, you're welcome.
But rice porridge is basically
the same no matter who makes it.
Fujimiya-san?
Uh...
Yeah, never mind.
Low Calorie
Easy to Drink Sports Drink
Hey, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Why were you sitting
on that swing in the rain?
Fight with your boyfriend or something?
Huh?
I hate to disappoint you,
but I have no boyfriend
and no plans to get one either.
Huh? Why?
I should be asking you.
Why are you assuming
that I'm in a relationship?
You're so popular,
I was sure you'd have a boyfriend or two.
Well, I don't.
I also don't recall
ever having such loose morals
that I'd go out with multiple boys at once.
That would absolutely never happen.
Sorry.
I didn't mean it that way.
I apologize.
No, I'm sorry I got that upset about it.
Anyway, I was just trying
to cool my head then.
But I am truly sorry
that it resulted in you catching a cold.
Nah, it's fine.
I didn't even ask you first.
You really shouldn't feel guilty about it.
I mean, we're done after this anyway, Shiina.
Huh?
Don't tell me you thought I was
guilt-tripping you to try to get lucky.
O-Oh.
I bet that's annoying even for you.
If guys you don't even like
keep coming on to you.
Well, it is, to be honest.
I knew it.
I don't really care, though.
Actually, it's kind of a relief.
Angels get annoyed by that
just like anyone else.
Please stop calling me that!
Well, like I said, I won't be trying
to hang around you for no reason.
Starting tomorrow,
we're basically strangers again.
Good morning!
I don't want to go to math.
Oh, Amane!
Are you feeling better?
Yeah, thanks a lot.
Yeah, I mean, you looked like a mess.
I was getting worried.
I'm glad you're better, though.
Just try to get your life together, okay?
Cleaning house, for starters.
You sound just like someone I know.
Huh?
Never mind.
Hey!
Shiina-san, can you please explain this part?
Of course. To solve this one,
just go like this.
Wow, I had no idea it was that easy!
Ah, Shiina-san, I see?
Thank you, Shiina-san!
Popular as usual, I guess.
You're very welcome.
She is an angel, after all.
A perfectly neutral observation.
For us, she's completely out of reach,
like a far-away dream.
I've got no reason to talk to her.
Seeing her around is enough.
What are you eating there?
A jelly drink that replenishes
energy in a few seconds.
That can't possibly be your dinner, is it?
What else would it be?
You've got the appetite of a high school boy
and that's all you're eating?
Please wait right there.
Huh?
What?
It's cold.
Wait? For how long?
Huh?
It's only leftovers, but here.
The Angel Next Door
Spoils Me Rotten
Tea
It's so good!
This is amazing, Angel!
I may be doing this for
my own personal satisfaction,
but I saw you living
such a pathetic lifestyle,
and I couldn't ignore it.
Quite so.
I'll happily accept it.
It isn't every day that I get
to eat an angel's home cooking.
Would you please stop calling me that?
Seriously.
Yeah, sorry.
I won't say it anymore.
You're going to start eating well
and living properly.
Sure, mom.
So good...
Shiina
Just returning this.
It was really good.
Thanks for going out of your way.
You even washed it for me.
Well done. So...
Here you go.
Huh? Yeah, no...
I just came to return the container.
It's tonight's dinner.
Yeah, I can see that, but...
I do need to ask,
do you have any food allergies?
I don't accept simple substitutions, though.
I don't, but...
I mean, I can't accept another...
I make too much to eat by myself.
I'd appreciate it if you would accept this.
If that's it, then I'm happy to help.
But normally, if you do this for someone,
they might think you have feelings for them.
You think I do?
No, not a chance.
Then it shouldn't be a problem.
In that case, please excuse me.
After that, the next day,
and the day after that,
Shiina kept handing me
containers full of food.
Life was starting to get weird.
So good...
Hey, Itsuki.
Do I really look that unhealthy?
Oh, yes! Pasty white and thin as a rail,
you always look like you're not into it.
Your expression just screams "unhealthy."
I was born with this face.
Oh, I know.
But why don't you try
to look a little more alive?
So that's it.
I've got a dead look on my face.
Yeah, but there is a little more color
in your cheeks recently.
Did you change your diet or something?
Itsuki...
You're scaring me right now.
Why, dude?
Wait, did I nail it?
No, well...
I was kind of forced
to mix things up, I guess.
10 servings
Delicious Rice
Oh...
Oh?
Just so you know, this wasn't intentional.
It's not like I'm following you.
Of course I know that.
This is obviously the closest
supermarket for both of us.
Customer Appreciation Sale
Limited to one per customer
Deal!
Limited to one per customer?
So I'm buying one too?
I'm glad you're such an understanding person.
10 servings
Delicious Rice
Tsuneno Milk
Rich Flavor
I didn't know you were
such a careful shopper.
There's no better way to keep costs down.
Well, if you're living on an allowance
from your parents, that's probably smart.
I guess so.
They do support me,
so it's important that I watch my budget.
Tsuneno Milk
Rich Flavor
100% Milk
I'm not trying to steal it.
I didn't think you were.
But I can carry that much.
In a situation like this, you'd seem a lot
more charming if you just accept the help.
You make it sound like
I have no charm at all.
I'll go ahead.
I know you don't want anyone
seeing us together.
Thank you very much.
Fujimiya
Huh?!
Excuse me, but yesterday's container...
What in the world are you doing?
I was trying to clean.
I just heard a really loud noise.
I almost tripped.
I'm not surprised.
It doesn't look like
you've even started cleaning.
Honestly, I don't know where to begin.
Your room—
please let me clean it.
Huh?
I can't stand the thought
of my neighbor living in filth.
Living alone and yet you do no chores...
Do you think this is some kind of a joke?
You know, if you had just cleaned regularly,
it never would have come to this.
'Tis as you say.
Just to warn you,
I'm going to do a very thorough job.
I understand.
As long as you do, shall we get started?
I'm not as soft as you might think.
We're not making any compromises.
Tie all the old magazines together.
Break down the cardboard and pile it up.
Tsuneno Milk
Water
Separate the lids from the plastic bottles.
Cleaning starts from the top.
Put all of your dirty laundry
in the basket for now.
Next, the top of the air conditioner.
Oh!
Fujimiya-san.
The reason you clean is to
keep things like this from happening.
Please accept my deepest apologies.
Should we keep going?
I guess so.
That surprised me!
All cleaned up.
It took a whole day to get this much done.
Yeah, the place was trashed.
You're the one who trashed it, you know.
'Tis as you say.
Oh boy...
I don't feel like going shopping now.
Want to order a pizza for dinner?
Huh?
So this is a delivery pizza.
You've never ordered delivery before?
Are your parents really strict about food?
At home, we had a housekeeper cook for us.
A housekeeper?
You must be pretty rich then.
I suppose you could say
we're somewhat well-off.
Well, I don't know if this is up to
your standards, but help yourself.
Thank you for the food.
What is it?
Nothing.
You're just making it look delicious.
Please don't stare at me so much.
How do I put this...
you really have zero charm.
That is fine with me.
Yeah, I guess that's okay.
I think I'm more used to
you here than at school.
I like this you more though,
because she's easier to get along with.
The one without charm, you mean?
You don't let things go, do you?
What I mean is,
even if you seem a little unfriendly,
you're a lot more approachable
when you're honest about your feelings.
Is my behavior at school really that awful?
Well, no.
But don't you get worn out
always acting like that?
Not really.
I've been like this since I was little.
That's pretty hard-core.
Well, at least you have a place
where you can catch your breath a little.
I can't catch my breath with your
staring always putting me on edge.
So sorry about that.
Fujimiya
Thank you for dinner.
Can I ask you one thing?
What is it?
What do you get out of sharing
your dinner with me every day?
My own satisfaction.
It's really not a big deal.
Simply put, I think I just like
preparing meals for people.
And you don't take that the wrong way,
you just tell me it's good, so it's easy.
I'm not comfortable with the way you eat
anyway, so I guess it's my own satisfaction.
Is that what this is?
That's what it is.
So just think of it as an unexpected
splash of good luck for you.
Well, well.
All right then, please excuse me.
I guess that's really all this is.
This is how the angel and I began
our unusual next-door relationship.
Next Time