[inspirational music playing]
[inspirational music swells]
[explosion]
He's here! Shoot him down!
[music intensifies]
[sword scraping]
- [both gasp]
- Kill him, now!
[clanking]
[whooshes]
[man gasps, groans]
[choking]
- [splashes]
- [screams]
[exclaiming in fear]
[gunshot]
[man yells]
Die!
[grunts]
[gasps]
- [choking]
- [man 2 exclaiming]
Ah, shit!
[gunshot]
[gasps]
[body thuds]
[men panting]
[grunts]
[inspirational music continuing]
[whooshes]
[gunshots]
[shatters]
[inspirational music continuing]
- [bodies thud]
- [exclaims]
Damn it, where did he go?
Where are you hiding?
Fucker! Come out here!
[narrator] There was once a hitman
said to be the greatest.
And his name...
...was Taro Sakamoto.
- [gunshot]
- [bullet casing clinking]
His prowess was unmatched.
All evil men feared him.
And all hit men revered him.
Until one day...
Huh?
- Good evening! How are you?
- [chimes]
[screaming echoes]
[glasses shatter]
- [narrator] ...Sakamoto fell in love.
- [chill music playing]
He retired...
- [kissing]
- ...got married,
had a baby,
and eventually...
Sakamoto grew...
out of shape.
[music fades]
[theme song playing]
[birds cawing]
THE LEGENDARY HIT MAN
SAKAMOTO'S
[Shin] This is the place.
Mr. Sakamoto, I've found you.
[wind blowing]
SAKAMOTO
- [glass squeaking]
- [boy] Watch this, mister!
If I hit the bullseye,
I get a free juice, 'kay?
I think that's quite enough for today.
That boy's been
hanging around a lot lately.
[Sakamoto] Mm-hm.
[boy laughs]
[grunts]
[boy] Aww, I missed!
- [Hana gasps]
- Okay, one more time!
- Let me try it one more time, mister!
- [bells chime]
BLACK INK
[sloshing]
Uh...
Oopsie...
How dare you, ya little brat!
- Look at what you did to my pants!
- [screams]
Goodness me!
- [man] Fix this!
- What do we do, dear?
- [boy whining] Come on, put me down!
- [growls]
[boy grunts]
Uh...
[gasps]
[straining]
You're dead!
Huh?
[groans]
[scoffs] Big fat creepy weirdo!
- [bells chime]
- Thank you. [crying]
Thank you, mister. [crying]
There, there.
Dry your tears.
Yeah, there, there!
- [Shin] Pretty impressive.
- [all] Huh?
Ballpoint pen to the carotid artery's
a rough way to go.
I saw what you were thinking.
[jazz music playing]
Mr. Sakamoto, it's been a while.
I'm Shin the Clairvoyant.
HIT MAN (CLAIRVOYANT) SHIN
[groan echoes]
[inner chime]
Why is killing me the first thought
that comes into your head?
Come on, it's me, Shin!
We used to be partners, remember?
[whimsical music playing]
I guess the rumors are true then.
A retired hit man
who gave up the life
to run a convenience store.
- [boy] Come on, hurry up!
- [kids laughing]
Please come back, Mr. Sakamoto!
You're wasting your talent!
And look at how fat you got.
[Sakamoto] I'll never be a hit man again.
[straining]
[Shin] You know, back in the day,
the worst of the worst feared you.
They called you the Legendary Assassin!
- [bangs]
- And now?
How did this happen?
[straining]
[blows]
[slurps]
[Sakamoto] Yummy.
I remember when
the only thing you ate were rations.
Honestly, I can hardly
recognize you, you're so--
[gasps]
[clicking]
[slurps]
[buzzer sound]
[Shin] Oh! So fast!
Is he trying to tell me
that even though he's out of shape,
he could kill me at any moment?
- [bicycle bell rings]
- Huh?
Hi there, Mr. Sakamoto!
Sorry to bug you in the middle of a meal,
but I wanted to ask for your help.
[Shin] What's this guy coming to him for?
[gasps]
Could it be a disguise
and he wants him to off somebody?
It needs a prune, but I can't reach
the branches up at the top.
So I figured, who else could I call?
[knife slashing]
Oh-ho, woah, wow!
I knew I could count on you!
BABY & CHILDREN'S GOODS
Mr. Sakamoto?
My daughter's not eating her vegetables.
[baby cooing]
- [mother] Mmm!
- Yummy!
- [crying]
- We can't play with only one ball!
- [gasps] Thanks, Mr. Sakamoto!
- [Shin straining]
[Sakamoto sighs]
What are you,
the handyman for the whole town?
[straining]
[chuckles] I get it now.
You're blending into your surroundings
so you can disguise who you really are.
But you know what, Mr. Sakamoto?
At least, as far as I'm concerned...
the new you is a big fat joke.
- See ya 'round.
- [plops]
[boy laughing]
[Shin] Little brat!
I can't believe it only took five years
for a guy like Mr. Sakamoto to go soft.
Although...
he was still so frickin' cool!
He may be fat
but you can't judge a book by its cover!
- I'd kill for the chance...
- [honking]
- ...to work with him again!
[woman gasps]
Look away!
- [Shin laughing]
- [honking continues]
[cell phone ringing]
BOSS
[beeps]
Hello?
[boss] You manage to convince him?
- Well, I... Not exac--
- [boss] So...
He still breathing?
- [tense music playing]
- [Shin] Boss...
I don't really think
that's necessary, do you?
You wouldn't believe
what a tub of lard Mr. Sakamoto is,
- he won't be a problem if we--
- Shin.
[sighs]
You know the rules.
You leave the organization without asking
and you die.
Sakamoto broke those rules.
That's why we can't let him live.
And remember this, Shin...
Whether you wanna do it or not,
I have an army of hit men!
So quit your whining
- or I'll put you in the groun--
- [beeps]
Ugh, get off my dick.
[sighs] I guess I don't have
much of a choice here.
- [scan beeps]
- [cash register beeps]
[tap creaks]
2 DAYS WORTH
[chill music playing]
[footsteps echoing]
[Shin] If I don't do it,
somebody else will.
And if it has to be done...
So be it.
I'll do it myself.
[boy] Hey, look!
What kinda poop do you think this is?
[Hana] Eww! That's gross!
Hello.
I remember you.
It was Shin, wasn't it?
Good to have you back so soon.
Lookit lookit!
Do you think this is alien poop?
[Shin] Can't help you, kid. Sorry.
Playtime's over, I'm afraid.
[squeaks]
[cash register dings]
A ROBBERY BREAKS OUT!
[bells chime]
Hiya, Mr. Sakamoto.
I'm leaving town.
I was hoping
I'd be able to stay a little longer.
But I thought I'd swing by first
so I could...
[chewing]
[suspenseful music playing]
...say goodbye!
[pops]
[intense music playing]
[cracking]
[clangs]
[gasps]
Was that a piece of candy?
[gasps, grunts]
[shudders]
[grunting]
Oh, great. He's hiding his thoughts.
- [thuds]
- [gasps]
Where is he?
[grunts]
[creaks]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[groans]
CUSTARD FILLING
Damn. I've gotta reposition.
[whooshes]
[gasps]
[objects clattering]
[thuds]
Ah, shit...
[intense music continuing]
What was I... thinking?
[groans]
[music fades]
[plates thud]
[Aoi] Dinner's almost ready.
Can you help me?
- [Hana] Okay!
- [exclaims]
[gasps] Hey, he's awake!
Oh! Well, thank goodness for that!
[straining]
Where the hell am I?
- [dog barking]
- [Aoi] On the second floor of the store.
You must be hungry.
- Care to join us?
- Eh?
- I...
- Do you want a super serving,
a mega one, or an ultra one?
A regular one, I guess?
Thanks for the food!
[Shin] What the hell is going on here?
He knows my mission... [gasps]
Maybe it's poisoned!
[scoffs] Well, I've spent years
building up my immunity.
[grunts]
[exclaims]
So good...
[emotional music playing]
And it's so warm...
[chuckles] It's just like the first time
you ate my cooking.
Just like you, Daddy!
[Shin] What is this?
Such a strange sensation.
In all my years on the job,
I've never felt so good.
[gasps] I get it now!
Ah.
[Shin] Mr. Sakamoto...
wanted to protect
this humdrum everyday life...
So he quit.
[emotional music continuing]
Mr. Sakamoto, I, um...
I appreciate the meal.
Hmm?
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU AGAIN
SAKAMOTO'S
[chuckles]
I should've known.
I'm no match for Mr. Sakamoto.
[footsteps approaching]
You wanted to see me, Shin? What?
Pathetic.
You couldn't get rid
of Sakamoto after all, could you?
Boss.
[boss] Save it.
I don't wanna hear your excuse.
I'm begging you, let Mr. Sakamoto live!
- [all laughing]
- [man] He's on his knees and everything!
Why would you want that?
Why are you covering for him?
He means something to people.
He's found a home in this town.
Sakamoto threw away his responsibilities.
He broke the rules of our world.
I gotta kill him.
If it's about responsibility,
then let me die in his place.
Just let him go.
Leave him alone!
You'd rather die instead?
I pointed a gun
at the person I admire the most.
This is how I make it right.
Fine then.
If you put a bullet in your own brain,
I'll spare Sakamoto.
- [inner chime]
- [scoffs] Yeah, right.
I'd never do that, you worthless fool.
Now hurry up and die.
- [intense music playing]
- Yeah, I heard that.
[men gasp]
And I can't really say I'm surprised.
[boss] Oh, right! He reads minds!
Ice this little prick!
- [Shin] Only one thing to do.
- [gunfire]
- [gunfire on headphones]
- [pensive music playing]
- [system chimes]
- [hisses]
[inspirational music playing]
[whirring, hissing]
[clanks]
[music fades]
[clicks]
[intense music playing]
[gunshots]
[gasps]
[gunfire]
[groans]
[man] You're gonna be Swiss cheese!
Huh? What? [grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
[man] Huh?
- [inner chime]
- [chuckles]
[man] I got a great shot from up here!
- [gasps]
- [explosion]
[groans]
Damn it!
- What are you doing? It's just one guy!
- [groaning]
It's like he knows what we're gonna do
before we do it.
That's because he's clairvoyant.
He can read your mind
if you get too close to him.
[man] Fan out and surround him!
[men panting]
[men gasp, groan]
- [gunfire]
- [grunts]
[panting]
[Shin scoffs] Down to my last mag.
Guess I'm gonna
have to push my way through.
[groans]
[groans] Shit!
[music stops]
[groans, grunts]
[gasps]
[gasps, shudders]
[straining]
I'm finished.
[electricity crackling]
[men screaming]
[groans]
[gasps]
[electricity crackling]
Mr. Sakamoto.
What's he doing here?
Kill him!
[growls] Die!
[intense music continues]
[thudding]
[clinks]
- [groans]
- [man] Son of a--
[groans]
[clinks, hisses]
[whooshes]
[gasps]
[man yelling]
[groans]
[man] I'll kill you!
[shouting]
[groans]
[clinking]
[panting]
[grunting]
[whooshes]
- [whooshing]
- [exclaims]
[groans]
- Die!
- [man yells]
[straining]
[men yelling]
WASTE
[thudding]
[groans]
[man] What just happened?
Die!
[groans]
- [groans]
- [knife clatters]
Shit. Quit going in one at a time.
- We have to shoot all at once!
- [shudders]
Light him up.
[gunfire]
[screams]
[men groan]
[boss] You bastard!
[Shin] Amazing.
There he is.
[thuds]
The Legendary Assassin.
Taro Sakamoto.
[gasps]
Mr. Sakamoto? How did you find me?
- [clicks]
- Huh?
You... You bugged my gun?
He must've put it there yesterday!
He hasn't let his guard down.
Mr. Sakamoto.
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
I already made up my mind.
It's over. I really am leaving town--
Uh...
SHIN
An apron?
You'll get eight hundred yen per hour.
And if you happen to work overtime,
it's paid.
[Shin] Eh?
[chill music playing]
- [door opens]
- [bells chime]
[boy laughing]
[Shin] Mr. Sakamoto?
Can you please
stop eating your ramen right next to me?
- [slurps]
- [groans]
I don't wanna mess up my brand-new shirt.
Huh? And our supply's
starting to run a bit low.
- [bells chime]
- [Hana] We're home!
Oh, wow!
- I think it suits you well, Shin.
- [Hana laughing]
Oh, you think so?
It suits you, Shin! [chuckles]
- [inner chime]
- Huh?
[old lady hesitating]
Here, ma'am. Detergent.
[old lady] Oh! How did you know?
That's just what I was looking for.
Thank you, dear.
Shin always knows!
Hey, come play with me.
As soon as I'm finished working.
[boy] Why? Is working here fun?
Uh, I don't know if it is or not yet.
But it beats the hell out of my last job.
- [boy] Why? What was your last job?
- [inner chime]
- [Sakamoto] If you say it, you're dead.
- [Shin shudders]
Uh, I was kind of a cleaner
for society.
[Sakamoto] Mmm.
[slurps, gulps]
[children laughing]
[girl] Come on, hurry up!
- [bells chime]
- [Shin] Hello! Welcome!
[theme song playing]